Contact

scott1021@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/brittany-scott-4b0679135 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Office Microsoft Word English

Certifications

Basic Life Support (BLS)

IV Therapy Certification (IVT)

CPR/AED/First Aid

Brittany Scott

Nurse Supervisor, LPN at Greenville Health & Rehab Greenville, Ohio

Summary

Skilled nurse with a history of being an experienced Nursing Assistant with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Experienced in Rehabilitation skilled care/services and long term care. Skilled in IV Therapy, CPR, Wound Care, Medication Administration, Point Click Care, Psychotherapy, and Microsoft Office. Strong healthcare service professional graduate from Miami Valley Career Technology Center.

Experience

Greenville Health & Rehab Nurse Supervisor, LPN December 2019 - Present (8 months) Greenville, OH

RESTHAVEN NURSING & REHABILITATION CENTER, LLC 8 years 6 months

LPN

March 2017 - November 2019 (2 years 9 months) Greenville, Ohio

State Tested Nursing Assistant June 2011 - March 2017 (5 years 10 months) Greenville, Ohio

- Assisted rehabilitative and restorative therapy for patients recovering from surgeries and trauma.
- Provided safe, one-on one care for daily living assistance to up to 15 residents while supporting accurate and timely documentation in long-term and skilled care units.
- Offered empathetic companionship and conversation to long term and skilled care patients to address physical, emotional, and social needs.
- Coached and trained new nursing assistants on how to follow plans of care to safely and effectively transfer and provide care to patients.

Preceptorship Nurse September 2016 - December 2016 (4 months) Greenville, Ohio

Practical Nursing Preceptorship

- Monitored and evaluated up to 15 assigned patients in the skilled care unit including documenting on vital signs, medications, and treatment progression under the supervision of an RN or LPN.
- Maintained documentation related to treatments, condition assessments, insulin use, nursing narratives, and more.
- Organized and administered patient teaching to patients and family regarding continued treatment, health risks, and proper home care.
- Delivered nursing services including: immunizations, wound and dressing care, g-tube feedings and care, glucose checks, respiratory treatments, skin care, ventilator and tracheotomy care, and more.

Brethren Retirement Community LPN Charge Nurse March 2017 - July 2017 (5 months) Greenville, Ohio

Education

Miami Valley Career Technical Center LPN, Practical Nursing (2016 - 2016)